This mailbox is mine,
so is this triagonal sign.
And that blue balloon,
the entire month of June,
it's all emphatically mine.
Mine-mine, mine-mine!
Ziggy's sweets, both of your feet,
you always knew they're mine.
It all belongs- belongs to me,
everything that I see, mine mine mine!
Oh, it's all mine.
This, mailbox is all mine,
and this triagonal sign.
And that blue balloon.
All belongs to me!
So the floor, and the ceiling,
are mine 'cause I'm the ruler,
it's all for me.
I can't help it!
Here's my kingdom, this is my crown.
It's made of gold, and it's so shiny.
I'm Stingy, I am a prince, easy to see...
I own everything!
Ziggy's sweets, both of your feet,
you always knew they're mine.
It all belongs to me,
everything that I see!
This, mailbox is all mine,
and this triagonal sign.
And that blue balloon.
All belongs to me!
The floor and the ceiling are mine, mine, mine, mine!
...emphatically mine...!
...it all belongs to me!
That's what I said:
It's mine!
It's MINE!